{
  "quiz": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Q. Which of the following is not a CSS box model property?",
      "choices": ["margin", "padding", "border-radius", "border-collapse"],
      "answer": "border-collapse"
    },
    
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Q. Which of the following is not a valid way to declare a function in JavaScript?",
      "choices": [
        "function myFunction() {}",
        "let myFunction = function() {};",
        "myFunction: function() {}",
        "const myFunction = () => {};"
      ],
      "answer": "myFunction: function() {}"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Q. Which of the following is not a JavaScript data type?",
      "choices": ["string", "boolean", "object", "float"],
      "answer": "float"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Q. What is the purpose of the this keyword in JavaScript?",
      "choices": [
        "It refers to the current function.",
        "It refers to the current object.",
        "It refers to the parent object.",
        "It is used for comments."
      ],
      "answer": "It refers to the current object."
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Q. Which method is used to convert JSON data into a JavaScript object?",
      "choices": [
        "JSON.parse()",
        "JSON.stringify()",
        "JSON.convert()",
        "JSON.object()"
      ],
      "answer": "JSON.parse()"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Q. Which array method creates a new array with elements that pass a condition?",
      "choices": ["map()", "forEach()", "filter()", "reduce()"],
      "answer": "filter()"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Q. What does the setTimeout function do?",
      "choices": [
        "Runs code repeatedly",
        "Runs code after a delay",
        "Stops code execution",
        "Clears a timer"
      ],
      "answer": "Runs code after a delay"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Q. Which keyword is used to declare a constant in JavaScript?",
      "choices": ["var", "let", "const", "static"],
      "answer": "const"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Q. Which HTML tag is used to include JavaScript?",
      "choices": ["<js>", "<javascript>", "<script>", "<code>"],
      "answer": "<script>"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Q. What will typeof null return in JavaScript?",
      "choices": ["null", "object", "undefined", "number"],
      "answer": "object"
    }
  ]
}
